appleinsider.com 2018-06-18

# Apple news and rumors since 1997 | AppleInsider

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to AppleInsider.com and its related sites. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. Below is information regarding AppleInsider's commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the internet. 

**User Information**

During your visit to the site, AppleInsider may collect your browser type and the IP address that your ISP designates to your machine (which, usually changes periodically depending on your type of internet connection) in order to statistically evaluate how we can design the site to best serve your needs. Any additional information may be specifically volunteered when you create an account through the AppleInsider discussion forums or article comment system. However, even then, AppleInsider does not use that stored information for any purpose other than to allow you to log in and post messages. 

**Cookies**

Along with countless other websites, AppleInsider uses cookies to enhance your experience. Cookies are used in the AppleInsider discussion forums to keep track of which messages have been posted since your last visit, enhancing the navigation of the forums. Cookies can also store your username and password so that you do not have to log in each time you want to post a message or comment on an article, though you must specifically request that this feature be turned on. Other user settings such as preferred site display options are also managed by cookies. 

Cookie data is not stored on the server, and therefore, not available for viewing by AppleInsider staff. However, it is possible that security flaws exist in some browsers that would allow other site administrators to write malicious scripts that would collect this data without AppleInsider's knowledge, though this is quite unlikely. 

When shopping through AppleInsider's Price Guides or through third-party links in posts, the corresponding merchant, website, or network may use cookies. Please refer to that specific site's privacy policy for more information. 

If you would like to opt-out of Non Personally Identifiable Information (PII) cookie tracking, please visit the NAI opt-out page here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. 

**Affiliate Link Disclosure**

Posts on AppleInsider.com and the corresponding Price Guides (prices.appleinsider.com) may include affiliate links, meaning AppleInsider may earn commission on purchases made through those links. 

Any commissions received as a result of AppleInsider's promotional efforts will not impact opinions on a product. If, through research and/or use, a product proves to be of benefit to the end-user, we will promote it. If not, we do not offer it. 

Affiliate referrals may utilize cookies, which are subject to the privacy policy of the corresponding merchant and/or affiliate network. 

**Third-party Service Providers**

A portion of the advertisements displayed on the AppleInsider Network are served by third-party advertisement providers, including Oath, Adblade, Conversant Media, Datonics, Exponential Interactive and Google. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

AppleInsider also periodically hosts product giveaways powered by Gleam or Rafflecopter. By entering the giveaway, participants agree to Gleam's privacy policy located here: <https://gleam.io/privacy> and Rafflecopter's Privacy Policy located here: <http://www.rafflecopter.com/rafl/privacy/>. No purchase is necessary to enter a giveaway hosted on AppleInsider.com. Giveaways are open to U.S. residents only. 

Please visit the National Advertising Initiative's opt-out management page for further information or to opt-out of behavioral advertising from many providers. 

We are committed to continuing to protect the privacy of our readers. If you have any additional questions, please contact us at Privacy@AppleInsider.com. 

We recommend that you review this Privacy Statement / Affiliate Link Disclosure periodically, as AppleInsider may update it from time to time without notice to its users. 

_This page was last updated on May 25, 2018._
